<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Dep Newaz Production</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/</link>
	<description>My WordPress Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 04:48:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.5.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/LogoMakr-6xurIF-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Dep Newaz Production</title>
	<link>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Third Post</title>
		<link>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/third-post/</link>
					<comments>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/third-post/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[newaz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/?p=136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Introduction: There was a time when a man would become a wonder to see birds fly in thy sky. But with the progress of science and technology, man has now become successful to fly in the air-though not like birds with wings, but by Aeroplanes. Now we can journey many places of the world by air &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/third-post/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Third Post</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Introduction:</strong> There was a time when a man would become a wonder to see birds fly in thy sky. But with the progress of science and technology, man has now become successful to fly in the air-though not like birds with wings, but by Aeroplanes. Now we can journey many places of the world by air within a very short time. It is the quickest means of travel the science and technology have ever produced.</p>
<p><strong>The occasion of my journey:</strong> I had a desire for a journey by air for long. At last the chance to fulfil my desire came to me when one of my maternal aunts living at Jessore asked me to see her at her house. She also sent me a ticket of Bangladesh Biman. As my School was closed for the S.S.C. Examination. I was very glad and thrilled at this offer of travelling by aeroplane. The journey was from Dhaka to Jessore.</p>
<p><strong>At the airport:</strong> As my flight was at 8.30 a.m. I reached the Dhaka airport at about 8 a.m. After the necessary formalities performed by the air officials, I boarded the plane at 8. 15 a.m.</p>
<p><strong>Taking off:</strong> Right at 8.30 a.m., the plane began to move. First, it ran slowly and gradually developing its speed, took off from the runway.</p>
<p><strong>Description of the journey:</strong> Our plane rose up at a legit of nine. hundred feet. It was flying very smoothly. I looked down through the window beside me. I became bewildered to see the land below. It appeared so little that it seemed to be a garden. Human beings appeared little like so many small ants and the houses like little matchboxes. The boats in the river and the motor vehicles on the streets seemed to be moving puppets. The rivers and canals below looked like zig-zag lanes. Soon I was lost in thought of the great power of the modern science. Just then an air hostess came and offered me snacks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/third-post/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Second Post</title>
		<link>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/second-post/</link>
					<comments>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/second-post/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[newaz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 04:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/?p=133</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bangladesh is riverine country. There are criss-crossed many big and small rivers. The Padma, the Meghna, The Jamuna are the big and wide rivers. The Buriganga, The sitalakshya, the Dhaleswari, the Teesta, the Madhumati, the Gumati and Karnafuli are small rivers. Most of the rivers of our country rise from the Himalayas and fall into &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/second-post/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Second Post</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bangladesh is riverine country. There are criss-crossed many big and small rivers. The Padma, the Meghna, The Jamuna are the big and wide rivers. The Buriganga, The sitalakshya, the Dhaleswari, the Teesta, the Madhumati, the Gumati and Karnafuli are small rivers. Most of the rivers of our country rise from the Himalayas and fall into the Bay of Bengal. There are hundreds of big and small rivers in our country. The rivers are the source of our wealth. Bangladesh is an agricultural country. The prosperity of agriculture depends on the river. These rivers have made the soil fertile. So ,rice. Jute, tea and other crops grow in plenty here. Our rivers are important for communication or transport. Boats, launches and steamers move on these rivers in all seasons. Men and goods are carried from one town to another, from one port to another. Most of the cities, towns, industries, hats, bazaars, trade centers are on the bank of rivers. The products of mills, factories and industries are easily carried to different places through rivers, Raw materials from far and near can be carried easily to our industries. Thus our rivers help in commerce, trade and industry. Some of our rivers are source of energy. Goalpara and Karnafuli hydro-electric projects are used to solve electricity problem. The rivers have are great influence on the people of our country. We love the rivers, its water and music. Much of our joys and happiness depend on rivers. Sometimes the rivers cause great damage to our life and property. In the rainy season the rivers overflow their banks and cause flood. People suffer untold sufferings. The rivers of Bangladesh help us lot in the progress and prosperity. In spite of the little harm, the rivers are useful to us in many ways. They are the source of our wealth, health ad happiness.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress_Proj_2/second-post/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
